But whatever. Yeah, that's all that we have. Let's try out this this one with posters right, right? So
I add the exact same description
But this time I say I want you to generate me a
poster
the poster
mentioning that and
Again
I choose the logo that I uploaded
This one I click select and the size yep and at the end I click create and
Again, wait a little bit
Until let's say my poster is generated
Okay, again, it says something's wrong on our end, but whatever it's removing my credits one after another
But that's all that we have, you know, the next step is that you wait and
It is supposed to generate you what you were looking for or whatever